Finding aid to Honorary Degree Files CA.MS.00006
Smith College Archives
- Series III. Board of Trustee - Committee on Honorary Degrees
  - Convocation - Honorary Degrees
    - 1970-71 (Box 86)
    - 1971-72 (Box 86)
    - 1972-73 (Box 86)
    - 1978-79 (Box 86)